Mr. President, thank you so much for having us here today and this roundtable.
Antifa is real.
Antifa has been around in various iterations for almost 100 years in some instances, going
back to the Weimar Republic in Germany.
And it's now been just under one month since we saw a far leftist murder Charlie Kirk,
and we saw thousands upon thousands of people, other far leftists and people in positions
of authority, people like nurses and pilots and doctors and HR departments, celebrating
the death and the murder of Charlie Kirk.
The sickness that's out there is absolutely real.
And Mr. President, thank you for mentioning the fact